DOCTOR: As you come into this
world. something else is also born.
You begin your life.
and it begins a journey.
towards you.
It moves slowly.
but it never stops.
Wherever you go.
whatever path you take.
it will follow.
Never faster. never slower.
Always coming.
You will run. it will walk.
You will rest. it will not.
One day. you will linger
in the same place too long.
You will sit too still
or slip too deep.
And when. too late.
you rise to go.
you will notice a second
shadow next to yours.
Your life will then be over.
(MACHINE POWERING UP)
(MAN GROANS)
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
(COUGHING)
(WHEEZING)
(DOOR HISSING)
(RAVEN CAWING)
DOCTOR: If you think
because she's dead I'm weak.
then you understand very little.
If you were any part of killing
her. and you're not afraid.
then you understand
nothing at all.
So for your own sake
understand this...
I am the Doctor.
I'm coming to find you.
and I will never. ever stop.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Ripped By mstoll
Happy New Year 2016 - New Year. New Color ;-)
The equipment in that room.
it's consistent with an
augmented ultra-long range teleport.
So I'm not more than a single
light year from where I was.
And I'm in the same time zone.
When the sun sets.
I'll be able to establish an
exact position by the stars.
then you'll have a choice.
Come out. show yourself.
or keep on hiding.
Clara said I shouldn't
take revenge.
You should know
I don't always listen.
Oh. what's this?
What. are you gardeners?
I hate gardening!
What sort of a person has
a power-complex about flowers?
It's dictatorship
for inadequates.
Or to put it in another way.
it's dictatorship.
Come on!
(CLAPPING) Chop. chop!
The Doctor will see you now.
Show me what you've got!
I just watched
my best friend die in agony.
my day can't get any worse.
Let's see what
we can do about yours.
(STATIC)
(GASPS)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(INSECT BUZZING)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(BREATHING ANXIOUSLY)
(GRUNTING)
I know you.
I've seen you before.
I used to know a trick.
Back when I was young
and telepathic.
Clearly. you can't make
an actual psychic link with a door
for one very obvious reason.
They're notoriously cross.
I mean. imagine life as a door.
People keep pushing past you.
all of the knocking.
but it's never for you.
and you get
locked up every night.
So if you are
just a little bit nice...
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
See. Clara?
I've still got it.
(SIGHS)
Right. (STAMMERING)
Uh...
I can't actually
see a way out of this.
Finally run out of corridor.
there's a life summed up.
(INHALES)
This isn't you.
I'm scared.
I just realised that
I'm actually scared of dying.
Something I said?
What did I say?
Why did you stop?
(RUMBLING)
(SNIFFING)
Old. Very old.
Possibly very. very old.
When I was a very little boy
there was an old lady who died.
(POPS) They covered her in veils.
but it was a hot. sunny day.
and the flies came. It gave me
nightmares for years.
So who's been
stealing my nightmares?
What am I here for?
And you've known about me
for a very long time. right?
So. what is it?
Is it a trap?
Is it a prison?
No!
Is it a torture chamber?
Am I right?
Somebody really
should know better.
Anyone who can put
all of this together.
and steal my bad dreams.
they should know better.
The secrets I have...
No chance. not telling. not me!
I told you I was scared of dying.
and I wasn't lying either.
Advantage. me.
Because you won't
see this coming!
Sorry I'm late.
Jumped out of a window.
Sudden death.
Don't you want to know how I survived?
Go on. ask me.
No! Of course I had to jump!
The first rule of being
interrogated is
that you are the only
irreplaceable person
in the torture chamber.
The room is yours. so work it.
If they're going to
threaten you with death.
show them who's boss.
Die faster!
And you've seen me do that
more often than most.
Isn't that right. Clara?
Rule one of dying. don't.
Rule two. slow down.
You've got the rest of your life.
The faster you think.
the slower it will pass.
Concentrate!
Assume you're going to survive.
Always assume that.
Imagine you've already survived.
There's a storeroom
in your mind.
Lock the door and think.
This is my storeroom.
I always imagine
that I'm back in my Tardis.
Showing off. Telling you
how I escaped. making you laugh.
That's what I'm doing right now.
I am falling. Clara.
I'm dying.
And I'm going to explain
to you how I survived.
Can't wait to hear what I say.
I'm nothing without an audience.
One hope. salt.
I thought I smelt it earlier.
when I broke the window. I'm sure.
Salty air. This castle
is standing in the sea!
Diving into water
from a great height
is no guarantee of survival.
I need to know exactly
how far I'm going to fall. and how fast.
Why do you think I threw the stool?
Fall time to impact.
(WATER SPLASHING)
DOCTOR: Seven seconds!
Because you won't see this coming!
The wind resistance of the stool.
the atmospheric density.
the strength of the local gravity.
Am I spoiling the magic?
I work with this stuff. you know.
Should hit the water in about...
.02 seconds.
The chances of remaining
conscious are...
(TARDIS POWERING UP)
(SCRIBBLING ON CHALKBOARD)
Can't I just sleep?
(SCRIBBLING CONTINUES)
Do I have to know everything?
Clara...
I can't lose.
(PANTING)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
It keeps coming. Clara!
Wherever I go. it follows. why?
Why does it do that?
Always the teacher.
What's the right question then?
(SCRIBBLING ON
CHALKBOARD CONTINUES)
It's following me.
Wherever I go. it's tracking me.
Slowly though. scary lurching.
Scary.
These screens everywhere.
it's showing me exactly
where it is all the time.
How far it's got. how near.
Because it's trying to scare me.
putting its breath on my neck.
That's the point.
That's what it's doing.
This is theatre!
It's all about fear.
A working hypothesis.
We're in a fully-automated
haunted house. a mechanical maze.
(CLATTERING)
It's a killer puzzle box
designed to scare me to death.
And I'm trapped inside it.
(CHUCKLES)
Must be Christmas.
(DISTANT CLANGING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
Another spade.
Someone wants me to take it.
What do you think. Clara?
Someone trying to give me a hint?
What would you do?
Yes. yes. of course you would.
Which. let's be honest.
is what killed you.
So...
Someone is trying to tell me that
there's something important
buried in this garden.
That's almost the first thing
they tried to tell me.
It could be a trick.
It could be one of
my predecessors.
Because I'm not
the first prisoner here. am I?
(ECHOING) All those skulls!
Wonder where they all went wrong.
A building this height.
a creature that slow. so what?
An hour.
(GRUNTING AND PANTING)
(FLY BUZZING)
(EXHALES)
(FLY CONTINUES BUZZING)
(SCREECHING)
(RATTLING)
Fifty-seventh time. you lose.
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(CREATURE HISSING)
So...
It can set traps.
That's okay.
I'm good at traps.
So where're you off to?
Only one way in and one way out.
Well. seeing as you're going.
(GRUNTING)
(EXHALES)
No. no. that's not right.
(METAL SCRAPING)
(SPADE CLUNKS)
(FLY BUZZING)
- (SCREECHING)
- (SCREAMS)
Well. that was another close one.
or it would've been
once I've been
and gotten myself out of it.
So how am I going to do that?
Come on. teacher. ask me questions.
(SCRIBBLING ON CHALKBOARD)
I'm actually scared of dying.
(SCRIBBLING CONTINUES)
The truth. yes.
But not any old truth. Clara.
This whole place is
designed to terrify me.
I'm being interrogated.
It's not just truth it wants.
that's not enough.
it's confession.
I have to tell truths
I've never told before.
That's the only thing
that stops it.
You see the problem is.
Clara...
...there are truths
that I can never tell.
Not for anything.
But I'm scared and I'm alone.
Alone...
And very. very scared.
I confess.
I didn't leave Gallifrey
because I was bored.
that was a lie.
it's always been a lie!
(GASPS)
Not enough? You want more?
I was scared.
I ran because I was scared.
Is that what you want me to say?
Is that true enough for you?
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
DOCTOR: It's funny.
The day you lose someone
isn't the worst.
at least you've got something to do.
It's all the days they stay dead.
- (FLIES BUZZING)
- (FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
Fifty-seven minutes.
This is how
my world works. Clara.
I tick off the seconds as they pass.
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
My life is a countdown.
If I draw the creature to
one extreme of the castle.
and I run to the other extreme...
I can earn myself
a maximum of 82 minutes.
(PANTING)
Eighty-two minutes to eat.
sleep and work.
My work is finding Room 12.
The castle wants me to.
It's luring me.
The numbering is a bit confused.
As if the rooms
are all jumbled up.
Maybe they move around.
I saw the whole castle move...
...when I made the creature stop.
Every room.
if I leave it long enough.
reverts to its condition
at the moment I arrived.
It tidies up after itself.
Automated room service.
I think this whole place
is inside a closed energy loop.
constantly recycling.
Or maybe I'm in hell.
That's okay.
I'm not scared of hell.
It's just heaven for bad people.
But how long
will I have to be here?
Forever.
(CLANGS)
It's always coming.
- (FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
- Always closer.
The countdown never stops.
But the countdown to what?
There are two events in everybody's
life that nobody remembers.
Two moments experienced
by every living thing.
Yet. no one remembers
anything about them
Nobody remembers being born
and nobody remembers dying.
Is that why we always
stare into the eye sockets of a skull?
Because we're asking.
"What was it like?
"Does it hurt?
"Are you still scared?"
DOCTOR: "Bird"?
What's a bird got to do with it?
Are there birds here?
(CLANGING)
(WIND WHOOSHING)
DOCTOR: There's something
I'm missing. Clara.
and I think it's something terrible.
(THUDS)
Hello?
Hello? Is there someone there?
Hello!
DOCTOR: It's a trap. Clara.
A lure and a trap.
I'm following bread crumbs
laid out for me.
This is somebody's game.
And I can't stop playing it.
A game everybody else has lost.
I know how to move
that wall. Clara.
So long as I don't
run out of confessions.
What I really want to know is...
Who's been playing
about with the stars?
- They're all in the wrong places.
- (FLY BUZZING)
For this time zone. anyway.
No! I didn't time travel to get here.
I can feel time travel.
If I didn't know better.
I'd say I've travelled
7.000 years into the future.
But I do know better.
So who moved the stars?
Behind me.
(FLY BUZZING)
Long before the Time War.
the Time Lords knew
it was coming.
Like a storm on the wind.
There were many
prophecies and stories.
Legends before the fact.
One of them was about
a creature called the Hybrid.
Half Dalek. half Time Lord.
The ultimate warrior.
But whose side will it be on?
Would it bring peace
or destruction?
Was it real or a fantasy?
I confess.
I know the Hybrid is real.
I know where it is and what it is.
I confess I'm afraid.
(RUMBLING)
(PANTING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
Of course!
The last square on the board.
What else would it be?
The Tardis.
One confession away.
(WHIRRING)
Spantium.
Four-hundred times
harder than diamond.
Twenty feet thick.
The way out.
Bird.
That's when I remember!
Always then! Always then!
It was exactly there!
I can't keep doing this. Clara.
I can't!
Why is it always me?
Why is it never
anybody else's turn?
(SCRIBBLING ON CHALKBOARD)
Can't I just lose?
Just this once!
Easy. It would be easy.
It will be so easy.
Just tell them.
Just tell. whoever wants to know
all about the Hybrid.
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
I can't keep doing this!
I can't!
I can't always do this!
It's not fair!
Clara. it's just not fair!
Why can't I just lose?
But I can remember. Clara.
You don't understand.
I can remember it all.
Every time.
And you'll still be gone.
Whatever I do.
you still won't be there.
CLARA: Doctor.
You are not the only person
who ever lost someone.
It's the story of everybody.
Get over it. Beat it.
Break free.
Doctor. it's time.
Get up. off your arse.
and win.
(FLY BUZZING)
Hello. again.
No more confessions. Sorry.
But I will tell you the truth.
(GRUNTS AND SCREAMS)
Ouch!
The Hybrid is a very dangerous secret.
A very. very dangerous secret.
And it needs to be kept locked!
(GRUNTS)
So I'm telling you nothing.
Nothing at all.
Instead. I'm gonna do
something far worse.
(GRUNTS)
I'm gonna get out of here.
And find whoever put me here
in the first place.
And whatever they're trying to do.
I'm going to stop it. Clara!
(GROANS)
(EXHALES)
It might take a little while.
Since you want me
to tell you a story.
(GRUNTS)
The Brothers Grimm.
lovely fellows.
They're on my darts team.
(GROANS)
According to them.
there's this emperor.
and he asks the shepherd's boy...
"How many seconds in eternity?"
(SCREAMING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(STATIC)
(TARDIS POWERING UP)
People always get it wrong
with Time Lords.
We take forever to die.
Even if we're too injured
to regenerate.
every cell in our bodies
keeps trying.
Dying properly can take days.
It's why we like to die
among our own kind.
They know not to bury us early.
(DOCTOR GROANS)
DOCTOR: I think.
in my current condition.
it will take me about
a day and a half to reach
the top of the tower.
(GRUNTS)
I think...
If I'm lucky.
I have a day and a half.
(GROANS)
I have to do this. Clara.
It's the only way.
I have to be strong.
I should have known
from the very beginning.
Of course.
The portrait of you.
the creature from
my own nightmares.
This place.
it's my own bespoke
torture chamber.
Intended for me only.
And all those skulls
in the water.
how could there be
other prisoners in my hell?
The answer of course...
Is there were never
any other prisoners.
And the stars...
They weren't in the wrong place.
And I haven't time travelled.
I've just been here.
(FEEBLY) A very. very...
...long time.
Every room resets.
Remember I told you that?
Every room reverts
to its original condition.
Logically.
the teleporter should do the same.
Teleporter. fancy word.
Just like 3D-printers. really.
Except they break down
living matter and information.
and transmit it.
All you have to do is add energy.
(GRUNTING)
The room has reset.
returned to its original
condition when I had arrived.
That means...
There's a copy of me
still in the hard drive.
Me...
exactly as I was
when I first got here
7.000 years ago.
(DOCTOR GROANS)
DOCTOR: All I have to find
is some energy.
And all you need for energy
is something to burn.
(GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(DOCTOR EXHALES)
DOCTOR: How long
can I keep doing this. Clara?
Burning the old me
to make a new one.
(TARDIS POWERING DOWN)
(COUGHING)
DOCTOR: If you think
because she's dead I'm weak.
then you understand very little.
If you were any part of killing her
and you're not afraid.
then you understand
nothing at all.
And so for your own sake
understand this.
I'm the Doctor.
I'm coming to find you.
And I will never ever stop.
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
Because you won't see this coming.
(GRUNTS)
DOCTOR: If I didn't know better.
I'd say I travelled
7.000 years into the future.
(GRUNTS)
"How many seconds
"in eternity?"
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(COUGHING)
If I didn't know better.
I'd say I travelled
12.000 years into the future.
(GRUNTS)
"How many seconds
in eternity?"
The shepherd's boy...
(SCREAMS)
(COUGHING)
(SCREAMING)
Six hundred thousand years
into the future.
(SCREAMS)
"How many seconds
in eternity?"
The shepherd's boy says...
(SCREAMS)
(COUGHING)
Twelve hundred thousand years
into the future.
(GROANS)
And the shepherd's boy says...
(COUGHING)
Two million years into the future.
And the shepherd's boy says...
(COUGHING)
(SHRIEKING)
Twenty million years
into the future.
Ow!
And the shepherd's boy says...
(GRUNTS)
"There's this mountain
of pure diamond.
"It takes an hour to climb it.
"And an hour to go around it."
(COUGHING)
Fifty-two million yea rs.
“Every hundred years.
"a little bird comes.
"It sharpens its beak
on the diamond mountain."
(COUGHING)
Nearly a billion years.
(GRUNTS)
"And when the entire mountain
is chiselled away.
"the first second in eternity
"will have passed."
(SCREAMS)
(COUGHING)
Well over a billion years.
(GRUNTS)
You must think
that's a hell of a long time.
(COUGHING)
Two billion years.
(GRUNTS)
Personally.
I think that's a hell of a...
(COUGHING)
(YELLS)
(CRACKING)
(EXHALES)
Personally.
I think that's a hell of a bird.
(LOUD THUD)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHOOSHING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Go to the city.
find somebody important.
tell them I'm back.
Tell them I know what they did.
And I'm on my way.
And if they ask you who I am.
tell them I came
the long way around.
You can probably still hear me.
So just between ourselves.
you've got the prophecy wrong.
The Hybrid is not half Dalek.
Nothing is half Dalek.
The Daleks
would never allow that.
The Hybrid destined
to conquer Gallifrey
and stand in its ruins...
...is me.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
ASHILDR: The Hybrid...
I think it's time to tell the truth.
WOMAN: I heard the Doctor
had come home.
One so loves fireworks.
MAN: What's he up to?
The Hybrid is a creature thought to be
cross-bred from two warrior races.
I know I went too far.
You have broken every code
you ever lived by.
On my command!
ASHILDR: Is it true?
DOCTOR: She's my friend.
- (LASER FIRE)
- (DOCTOR SCREAMING)
Red Team to Sector 52.
extraction chamber 7.
Regeneration in progress.
Ripped By mstoll
Happy New Year 2016 - New Year. New Color ;-)